<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>caginagirdemir.github.io/blog/</title>
        <link>http://example.org/</link>
        <description>caginagirdemir.github.io/blog/</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 01:41:08 &#43;0300</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Serial EEPROM Writer</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/eeprom-writer/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 01:41:08 &#43;0300</pubDate><author>
            <name>Cagin</name>
            <uri>http://example.org/authors/cagin</uri></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/eeprom-writer/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Remote Plug Tracing and Control System ProjectSince It was my Bachelor dissertion which can measure plug current (for estimate your electrcity bill) and control. I used to tell another post with details. The program is written for my undergraduate thesis. Works with ESP82266. It makes a wifi call and you can enters the password and saves wifi information to the device&rsquo;s eeprom via usb. Developed with C #.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Certification</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/certification/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
            <name>Cagin</name>
            <uri>http://example.org/authors/cagin</uri></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/certification/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[IBM Python Essentials This certificate was about Python Essentials and essentialy Data Science. I learned Python Data Science Libraries.
Embedded Systems It was a essential embedded system course based on C programming language. There was some essentials subjects such as if statement, loop statements. Also there was a little bit more complex structures like finite program structure.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Joystick Kit</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/joystick/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
            <name>Cagin</name>
            <uri>http://example.org/authors/cagin</uri></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/joystick/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Video   Kitlab Engineering Kitlab Engineering is a brand formed by me. I uses this brand name when I make a STEM Educational Kit.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Robotic Kit</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/robotic-kit/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
            <name>Cagin</name>
            <uri>http://example.org/authors/cagin</uri></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/robotic-kit/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Robotic Kit I designed a new robotic kit which include Arduino UNO, Bluetooth, 4 various sensor. This kit completely printable with 3d printer. Also, this kit include a tray system; so students can be made themselves design in tune with tray gaps.
This kits consist of 11 part.
Specifications  Arduino UNO R3 Settled Bluetooth Module Distance Sensor (Ultrasonic) Unlimited sensor connectable with settled breadboard Buzzer, RGB Led, Tempature and Humid Sensor  I was build just 28$]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>TESOL Certification</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/tesol-certification/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
            <name>Cagin</name>
            <uri>http://example.org/authors/cagin</uri></author><guid>http://example.org/posts/tesol-certification/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Tesol Certification"Tesol Certification Content I took this certification from Arizona State University.
I took some courses as followings:
 Foundational Principles Theories of Second Language Acquisition Lesson Design and Assessment Teaching Reading, Writing, and Grammar Teaching Listening, Speaking, and Pronunciation Technology-Enriched Teaching  I had abservation 10 hours and also teach 10 hours]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
